Muhammad Zubair

Lahore

muhammadzubair489_cio@indeedemail.com

(+92) 334 6278185

Objective:

To achieve Professional excellence and a professional attitude in my career, progress towards advancement based upon motivations and achievements within the business environment.

Overview:

Over the last 8 years, I have developed a wide range of websites and web systems using PHP, Laravel Codelgniter, Node JS, Angular, Vue Js, WordPress (CMS), Ionic, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and MySQL including sites for startup companies, small businesses, and grown companies.

Work Experience

Sr. Software Engineer

MateebTech January 2020 to Present

Sr. Software Engineer

Seers Group
March 2018 to December 2020

Sr. Software Engineer

Creative Village Studios February 2013 to February 2018

Software Engineer

OffRoad Studios September 2011 to January 2013

Education

BS Hons in Computer Science

Islamia University 2007 to 2011

Skills

- Laravel
- Vue Is
- Nodels
- AngularJS

- PHP
- Laravel
- VueJS
- WordPress
- Git
- Bootstrap
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- MySQL
- Mongo DB
- Adobe Photoshop